Oh, she's here. Hey, Akane! You are so great!
Yeah, sorry.
They needed a last-minute cover, so I got called into work last night.
Then I had to work on my report, so I hardly got any sleep.
No way, for real.
Since convenience stores are always so understaffed, they can be a tough job to handle.
You guys! Let's get in on the fun already!
Could that person with the rabbit ears and joyous look in their eyes be Eita?
He's got a horde of girls snapping pics of him.
Yeah, Eita adores festivals like these.
Eita?
Hey, wait! Where are you going, guys? Wait up for me!
No, don't leave me!
So this is Yamada's school, huh?
I'm here.
Yeah.
Would you look at the variety of stalls they have here?
Hey, Runa, do you see anything you like to eat?
Runa's not hungry.
Huh?
Poor Runa.
She must be nervous because she'll be taking the entrance exam for this school next year.
Oh.
It's okay, Runa. Just relax.
This could be a great chance to get the lay of the land.
Runa's insecure, so she can't.
Welcome to our cafe!
I wanna go! I wanna go! Come on, let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Have fun, you two!
We've got two new patients! I'm sending them in!
So, where should we go, then?
Takodaki, come and get them out!
Go!
Come on! Come on, let's go!
Oh?
My stomach hurts...
I'm so nervous, I'm getting a tummy ache!
I can't do this...
I can't do this. If I'm this fragile, I'll fail the entrance exam.
Hey, stop that. Let's find a restroom.
Mr. Kamata and I just exited the haunted house, and we're going to look around some more.
Let's meet up in about 15 minutes.
Okay, sure.
That reminds me. I wonder if Yamata's going to join us at some point.
I'll ask him.
Wait, if I just ask him out of the blue like that, he might think that I want to see him or something.
Nah, I don't need to ask. I'll probably find out later anyway.
What the? How did that happen?
Is everybody all right?
Oh, what a mess.
Oh, dang. Are you guys okay? We can take care of it for you.
Thanks so much.
Bring it in.
Yamata!
Kishida from ethics class is taking part in the first year's fighting game tournament, but his moves are all over the place.
He's kind of...
hard to approach right now.
Will he look this way, maybe?
I'll help out.
Hey, Yamata!
Oh, there he goes.
Well, it is what it is.
He seemed busy anyway.
Of course you wouldn't notice me.
For heaven's sake.
Oh.
I told them to start putting away the boxes they were done with first, but they just leave them out wherever.
I know, everyone around here is so sloppy, aren't they?
Tsubaki, is it all right if I step out?
Yeah, that's fine with me.
But where to?
No, we're special.
She's been in there a while.
Maybe I should go check on her.
Are you here alone?
Oh, did you notice I was here?
Yes.
I was going to call out to you, but then we had some trouble.
Anyway, why are you here all alone?
And why are you smiling?
Oh, uh, no reason.
Runa's pretty nervous.
It was so bad she got a stomachache.
So she's been taking a breather in the restroom.
But it's been a while and I'm starting to get worried.
I was just about to go check on her when you showed up.
I can't do it.
There's no way I can make it through the real entrance exam like this.
Well, you don't have a fever, so lie down a bit and we'll see how you feel.
I can't do it.
No, no, no, you can't.
Don't tell Aunt about this or he's still going to take me home.
I can't do it.
I can't do it, Ellen.
But I still haven't eaten any yummy food yet and I haven't had any fun.
I thought you had a stomachache.
But Bruna still wants to eat all kinds of food.
That's the reason I haven't had even a single bite to eat since last night.
That's not your problem.
Oh, if that's all, I'll just go buy some stuff for you.
Then you can eat it when you're feeling better, okay?
Okay.
I want a crepe and a cheese dog and takoyaki.
They were selling pork miso soup in the courtyard, so I want some of that too.
And I just have to have a limited edition festival t-shirt.
Yeah, sure, sure.
And where do they sell the festival teas?
I'll take you there.
See you later.
Yamada, so is it okay for you not to be working with your classmates?
Yes.
I was going to take off in the afternoon anyway.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's backstage work, so we're pretty free once it's underway.
Oh, really?
What's your class doing then?
Something fun?
We teamed up with the class next door to make a giant labyrinth outside.
Anyway, why does it feel like everyone is staring at us?
Oh, you noticed too?
Thank goodness.
I better watch my back.
I'm going to walk ahead.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, Yamada, how's it going?
So this is where you've been wandering, huh?
You know I hear you're finally taking part in the pageant show this year.
Guess you couldn't escape it for the whole three years, huh?
Ha!
Huh?
Whoa-ho!
Look at you!
You're with the girl, huh?
Here I thought you were a perverse guy, not caring how popular you were.
But I think you're gonna make me change my tune, you punk.
There you go, Yamada. That's my boy.
Oh, we've never met before.
Which high school do you go to, young lady?
Oh, uh, no. I'm a college student, and I...
So you're older?
Ah, I see. You're into older women, are ya?
Good for you.
Thanks, kid. You've really made my day.
Oh, wow. That teacher seems like he's a real ball of energy.
He teaches PE.
I see.
Yamada-senpai!
Is that pal standing next to you your girlfriend?
A woman you've been dating?
Who is she?
We're thorough over women.
Who are they?
First years, I think. Judging by their shoe color.
Gotta hand it to youth.
Uh, I'm not his girlfriend.
So you're really not dating them?
Do you mean it?
Then why are you two walking together?
Yeah, Yamada-senpai, why?
Who is that person to you?
What a blonde girl for women?
Oh, what a girl's response to the answer.
Huh.
We finally managed to make it out of the building.
I'm totally exhausted.
Hey!
Oh, and look at that. Akito's with her, too.
We bought a whole bunch of stuff.
So, Runa's got a stomachache, does she?
Huh?
Hey, Akaneci, did you get older?
Hear me out, both of you.
It was such an ordeal just getting outside, you know?
Let me guess.
The campus was abuzz because Akito was with a girl, am I right?
Same thing happened to Runa last year.
Well, this was no joke.
You should have seen their eyes.
It's like they were less convinced
because I was denying being his girlfriend at all.
I sure wish I was there.
I'd love to see you swaggering about
crushing all those girls' hopes and dreams.
That's not how it was.
We're just friends.
Hmm. Well, if they're gonna glare anyway,
why not give them a reason to?
Why don't you two just, you know, start dating?
Right, Akito?
Uh-huh. Well, yeah, I suppose so.
Huh?
Isn't Akanechi's cheery nature great?
I guess.
Her hobby's online gaming, so you're like a perfect match.
Excuse me, you're way out of line!
Alright, you're officially a couple now.
Nah, just kidding.
Uh...
Um...
Akanechi?
Oh, sorry.
What?
It was just a joke.
I'm so sorry, really. I was just teasing Akito a little, okay?
Oh, a joke.
That's right. I'm sorry.
I still have a lot of shopping to do! Bruno wants food!
Uh, Akanechi, hey!
Akane, please don't go!
I hate you, Eita!
Don't you try giving me a hard time either!
Darn it all!
Aw...
Crap.
Akanechi got hurt because I was messing with Akito.
You two wait here, okay?
I'll go apologi-
I could have handled that better.
Why don't you two just, you know, start dating?
Ha ha ha. Okay, you've had your fun now.
That would have been the right response.
But here I am.
music
It's pretty vanished
I'm sorry.
Well, I see it.
It's...
Can I see?
Menguidел
Mrs.
why am i like this i must have looked like a crazy person and yamada was just sitting
there with a blank stare on his face oh talk about embarrassing
oh i'm so sorry please don't rush through the hall so carelessly
hey wait stop running
there you are yamada is that person with you
akane please stop for a second
the stairs it's not safe
don't let her run okay
sorry about all that with eta
you just said my name for the first time
huh no that can't be true though
but it is true i'm sure that was the first time
i mean you like never call me by my name and you've gone so long without saying it the whole time we've known each other i was convinced you didn't know it
that's ridiculous
so uh about what happened outside earlier
come over here with me
sorry for dragging you like that i needed to get away from there
i couldn't ignore those murderous looks anymore
is that what you were feeling
anyway i'm sorry about earlier
i honestly had no intention of teasing you
i knew that eta was joking around like usual
so i played along
hey hold on look i'm not mad or anything so let's not talk about it
huh
so you're not mad
but a second ago you were definitely angry
i really wasn't trust me
it's just that
i
i guess the whole thing made me a little embarrassed
so i ended up
saying all those things
sorry but
which part of that made you feel embarrassed
can you please stop asking me about it
so
you really aren't mad then
i told you i'm not mad at all
i'm glad to hear that
okay
do you want to go shopping
hey what if
i mean
what if i had taken eta's joke seriously
and said
okay i'll start dating yamada
if that was what i said
what would you have done
well yamada
nah
i'm just kidding
you never know if someone might take a joke seriously like that
so you shouldn't play around with romantic stuff so nonchalantly
you understand
right
right then let's go
why am i like this
if that did happen
i'd probably say
that it'd be a real honor
however
for someone who's a nobody like me
the truth is akane
you're like a flower that i can't reach
so i've never really thought about it before
what are you being serious with me
yes
then are you saying
that's how you've been seeing me this whole time
uh-huh
what were we supposed to buy again
hey wait for me
a crepe
a cheese dog
some takoyaki
and pork miso soup
also
i think you're a fun guy yamada
for real
you
Come on, Yamada. Won't you take one for the team and just enter the pageant, pretty please?
I already told you what's not happening.
Aw, come on, man. Don't be like that.
See there? All of them want you.
Hm?
You see?
Still no.
Please, dude. This is our last festival.
Don't you want your very last one to be the most memorable of all?
Don't you?
I guess being too handsome comes with the TEDx.
And he's totally cracked at games, too.
Not fair.
Please do it today. It's our last.
Don't you think you should go save him now?
Sure, if you say so.
Count me in!
Huh?
Okamoto, what do you think you're doing?
You can leave it all to me.
And now, the moment you've been desperately waiting for has finally arrived!
Here comes the guy who's been refusing to enter the Mr. Tosek contest for two years running!
Entry number six.
Class 3A, Akito Yamada!
Now, batting for Yamada, pinch hitter, Okamoto!
Weibo!
Yamada Senpai!
Take that time, Okamoto!
No one else for you!
Hey there!
My favorite things to eat are hamburgers and fries!
Things I can't stand are campers and snipers!
I'm Takeaki Okamoto!
Vote for me!
Go, Okamoto!
You got this, Okamoto Senpai!
For real, right now, we want to see Yamada Senpai!
Get it, Okamoto!
Make this place rock in Yamada's honor!
What the heck's a camper, though?
Please, everybody, if you're gonna shout, follow the rules!
You do know you owe him a hamburger later, don't you?
Yeah, sure.
Can your big bro have some?
Come on, big bro's starving.
Just one teensy bite.
Ready?
No way.
Is in pain.
Just one teensy bite.
Sent crazy.
It is, was the biggest, uh...
Serend月?
Smoled herself.
This is wild.
Ooh.
Wow.
Gonna prepared you.
です.